Register of the Kenneth Gibson Fuller collection
Hoover Institution Archives
Kenneth Gibson Fuller collection
1960-1994
93061
Hoover Institution Archives
57 manuscript boxes (23.8 linear feet)
The Kenneth Gibson Fuller collection contains leaflets, pamphlets, and serial issues, mostly related to the New Left and counter-culture in the San Francisco Bay Area between 1965 and the mid-1970s. Many of the materials concern protests and demonstrations at the University of California at Berkeley and the area around the campus. These include announcements of anti-war and other protests, as well as leaflets and serial issues regarding the 1969 events surrounding People’s Park. While there is a major focus on Berkeley, the collection does contain publications from around the Bay Area, including Stanford University, San Jose, and San Francisco. There are also some documents pertaining to radical activism in Southern California, New York City and Madison, Wisconsin, as well as publications with a larger national and international emphasis.
Fuller, Kenneth Gibson, collector.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1993.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content of Collection
The Kenneth Gibson Fuller collection contains leaflets, pamphlets, and serial issues, mostly related to the New Left and counter-culture in the San Francisco Bay Area between 1965 and the mid-1970s. Many of the materials concern protests and demonstrations at the University of California at Berkeley and the area around the campus. These include announcements of anti-war and other protests, as well as leaflets and serial issues regarding the 1969 events surrounding People’s Park.
While the focus is on Berkeley, the collection does contain publications from around the Bay Area, including Stanford University, San Jose, and San Francisco. There are also documents pertaining to radical activism in Southern California, New York City and Madison, Wisconsin, as well as publications with a larger national and international emphasis.
The publications and flyers collected by Fuller record the significant issues that preoccupied the New Left and the protest movements of the 1960s and 1970s: the Vietnam War, above all else; black militancy, especially that exemplified by the Black Panther Party; political trials and prisoners’ rights; the women’s and gay liberation movements; and the condition of the American working class. By definition, the leaflets in the collection qualify as ephemeral and fugitive materials, but many of the pamphlets and serial issues fall under this category as well. Most of the serial issues had limited runs and, as the heyday of radical activism passed, many went out of existence.
In terms of the serial issues in the collection, many were published by rival Marxist-Leninist organizations seeking to establish themselves as the vanguard party for what they believed would be an eventual revolution in the United States. However, there are also many generic New Left groups that figure in the materials. In these documents, one can trace the evolution of the New Left from its origins in the mid-1960s to the factional disputes that roiled the student movement in 1969 and afterwards. Other serial issues relate to the counter-culture of the 1960s and early 1970s and have a less political tone to them. In its breadth and extent, the collection complements the New Left collection in the Hoover Institution Archives, and it is an important resource on American radicalism and the counter-culture in the era of the Vietnam War.
University of California, Berkeley.; Student movements--United States.; Radicalism--United States.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975--Protest movements.
- Leaflets and Pamphlets, 1960-1994 (Boxes 1-21)
  - Abortion, 1964 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Africa, 1966-1977 (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Africa Research Group, 1970 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1967-1975 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - American Federation of Teachers, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Americans for Democratic Action, 1964 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Anarchists, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Anti-war movement, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 1: 8-9)
  - Anti-war movement, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 2: 1-5)
  - Anti-war movement, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 3: 1-6)
  - Anti-war movement, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 4: 1-5)
  - Anti-war movement, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - Asia, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - Asian Americans, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 5: 3)
  - Associated Students of the University of California (ASUC), 1965-1970 (Box-folder 5: 4-5)
  - Bay Area Research Collective, 1975 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - Berkeley city politics, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 5: 7)
  - Berkeley city politics, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Berkeley Commune, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Berkeley Tenants Union, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Black Panthers, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Boalt Hall Action Committee, 1970 (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - Brown, George, 1970 (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - California State College at Hayward, 1970 (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - California state politics, 1965-1980 (Box-folder 6: 8)
  - Center for Participant Education (CPE), 1969-1971 (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Chemical and biological warfare, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - Chicago convention, 1968 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - China, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Chomsky, Noam, 1967 (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - Christian organizations, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 7: 4)
  - Civil rights movement, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 7: 5-6)
  - Columbia University, 1968 (Box-folder 7: 7)
  - Communist Party USA, 1965 (Box-folder 7: 8)
  - Community for New Politics, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 7: 9)
  - Council of Campus Organizations, 1965 (Box-folder 7: 10)
  - Counter-culture, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 7: 11)
  - Counter-culture, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 8: 1)
  - Cuba, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 8: 2)
  - Davis, Angela, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 8: 3)
  - Death penalty, 1965 (Box-folder 8: 4)
  - Dellums, Ron, 1970 (Box-folder 8: 5)
  - Diggers, 1967 (Box-folder 8: 6)
  - Economics, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 8: 7)
  - Education, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 8: 8-9)
  - Energy crisis, 1974 (Box-folder 8: 10)
  - Environment, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 8: 11)
  - Farmworkers, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 9: 1-2)
  - Firearms, 1969 (Box-folder 9: 3)
  - France, 1968 (Box-folder 9: 4)
  - Free Speech Movement, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 9: 5-6)
  - Free University of Berkeley, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Frontlash, 1970 (Box-folder 9: 8)
  - Gay liberation, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 9: 9)
  - Hayden, Tom, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 10: 1)
  - High school students, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - Ho Chi Minh, 1972 (Box-folder 10: 3)
  - Horowitz, David, 1969 (Box-folder 10: 4)
  - Independent Socialist Club, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 10: 5)
  - India, 1972 (Box-folder 10: 6)
  - International Hotel, 1977 (Box-folder 10: 7)
  - International Socialists, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 10: 8)
  - Iran, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 10: 9-11)
  - Ireland, 1970 (Box-folder 10: 12)
  - Labor movement, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 10: 13)
  - Labor movement, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 11: 1-2)
  - Latin America, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 11: 3)
  - Leary, Timothy, 1970 (Box-folder 11: 4)
  - Left Alliance, 1970 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Libertarians, 1970 (Box-folder 11: 6)
  - Mandel, Ernest, 1969 (Box-folder 11: 7)
  - McCarthy, Eugene, 1968 (Box-folder 11: 8)
  - McGovern, George, 1972 (Box-folder 11: 9)
  - Medical cadre, 1970 (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - Mexican Americans and Chicano movements, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Mexico, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Middle East, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 12: 1-3)
  - Midpeninsula Free University, 1970 (Box-folder 12: 4)
  - Military research, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 12: 5)
  - National Caucus of Labor Committees (NCLC), 1974 (Box-folder 12: 6)
  - Native Americans, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 12: 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM), 1972 (Box-folder 12: 8)
  - New Dawn, 1975 (Box-folder 12: 9)
  - Newton, Huey P., 1968-1972 (Box-folder 12: 10)
  - Non-violence, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - North American Congress on Latin America (NACLA), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 13: 2)
  - October League, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Peace and Freedom Party, 1968 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - People's Park, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 13: 5-6)
  - Political trials, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Political trials, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 14: 1-3)
  - Prisoners, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 14: 4-5)
  - Progressive Labor Party (PL), 1965-1975 (Box-folder 14: 6)
  - Progressive Labor Party (PL), 1965-1975 (Box-folder 15: 1-2)
  - Puerto Rico, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 15: 3)
  - Racism, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 15: 4)
  - Radical Education Project, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15: 5-6)
  - Radical Student Union (RSU), 1969-1972 (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1969 (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC), 1968-1970 (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - Revolutionary Student Brigade, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Revolutionary Union (RU), 1968-1972 (Box-folder 16: 5)
  - San Francisco State University student strike, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 16: 6)
  - Scheer, Robert, 1966 (Box-folder 16: 7)
  - Science and technology, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 16: 8)
  - Situationists, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 16: 9)
  - SLATE, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 16: 10)
  - Socialist Labor Party, 1968 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Socialist Party and Young People's Socialist League (YPSL), 1968-1972 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Socialist Workers Party (SWP) and Young Socialist Alliance (YSA), 1965-1975 (Box-folder 17: 3-5)
  - Sociology, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Soviet Union, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Spartacist League, 1965-1983 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Stanford anti-war movement, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 18: 3)
  - Student West Oakland Project, 1968 (Box-folder 18: 4)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), 1964-1972 (Box-folder 18: 5-7)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), 1964-1982 (Box-folder 19: 1-2)
  - Symbionese Liberation Army, 1974 (Box-folder 19: 3)
  - Third World Liberation Front (TWLF), 1969 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Turkey, 1965 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - University of California at Berkeley campus issues, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 19: 6-7)
  - University of California at Berkeley campus issues, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 20: 1-3)
  - University Young Democrats, 1965 (Box-folder 20: 4)
  - Venceremos College, 1970 (Box-folder 20: 5)
  - Weatherman and Weather Underground, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 20: 6)
  - W. E. B. Dubois Clubs, 1967 (Box-folder 20: 7)
  - Welfare rights, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - White Panthers, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 20: 9)
  - Women's liberation, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 20: 10-11)
  - Women's liberation, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 21: 1)
  - Yippies, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 21: 2)
  - Yoga, 1969 (Box-folder 21: 3)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF), 1969 (Box-folder 21: 4)
  - Young Lords, 1969 (Box-folder 21: 5)
  - Zapata, Emiliano, 1973 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Zinn, Howard, 1970 (Box-folder 21: 7)
- Monographs and Reports, 1961-1973 (Box 21)
  - 1961 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - 1965 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - 1966 (Box-folder 21: 10-11)
  - 1968 (Box-folder 21: 12)
  - 1969 (Box-folder 21: 13)
  - 1970 (Box-folder 21: 14)
  - 1972 (Box-folder 21: 15-16)
  - 1973 (Box-folder 21: 17-18)
- Serial Issues, 1964-1991 (Boxes 22-57)
  - 2...3...Many, 1970 (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - 1917, 1986 (Box-folder 22: 2)
  - Action, 1970 (Box-folder 22: 3)
  - Activist, 1966 (Box-folder 22: 4)
  - ADA World, 1965 (Box-folder 22: 5)
  - Adult Reporter, 1968 (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Advocate, 1974 (Box-folder 22: 7)
  - African Liberation Support Committee Newsletter, 1977 (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - African World, 1975 (Box-folder 22: 9)
  - Ain't I a Woman?, 1970 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Aion, 1970 (Box-folder 22: 11)
  - Akwesane Notes (Box-folder 22: 12)
  - Ally, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 22: 13)
  - Alternative, 1976 (Box-folder 22: 14)
  - American Communist, 1970 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - American Report, 1971 (Box-folder 22: 16)
  - American Student, 1970 (Box-folder 22: 17)
  - Anarchy, 1967 (Box-folder 22: 18)
  - Ang Katipunan, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 22: 19)
  - Ann Arbor Argus, 1969 (Box-folder 22: 20)
  - Anti-Fascist Commentator, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22: 21)
  - Anti-Imperialist Newsletter, 1973 (Box-folder 22: 22)
  - Anvil, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Aphra, 1969 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - Appeal to Reason, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 3)
  - Aquarius, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - Arab Student Bulletin, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 23: 5)
  - Argentina Outreach, 1976 (Box-folder 23: 6)
  - Argo (Box-folder 23: 7)
  - ARIS, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - Arm the Spirit, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 23: 9)
  - Asian Student, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - Attica News, 1975 (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - Augur, 1969 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Auto Workers Focus (Box-folder 23: 13)
  - Babylon, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 23: 14)
  - Barb on Strike, 1969 (Box-folder 23: 15)
  - Barricade (Box-folder 23: 16)
  - ¡Basta Ya!, 1969-1972
    - 1969 (Box-folder 23: 17)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 24: 1)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 24: 2)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 24: 3)
  - Bay Area Asian Coalition Against the War Newsletter, 1972 (Box-folder 24: 4)
  - Bay Area High School Free Press, 1969 (Box-folder 24: 5)
  - Bay Area Reporter, 1972 (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - Bay Area Socialist, 1970 (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Bay Area Worker, 1972-1975
    - 1972 (Box-folder 24: 8)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 24: 9)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 24: 10)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Bayviewer, 1968 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Berkeley Citizen, 1967 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Berkeley Fascist, 1969 (Box-folder 25: 3)
  - Berkeley Holistic Health Center, 1978 (Box-folder 25: 4)
  - Berkeley News, 1975 (Box-folder 25: 5)
  - Berkeley Observer, 1970 (Box-folder 25: 6)
  - Berkeley Teacher, 1975 (Box-folder 25: 7)
  - Berkeley Times, 1967 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Bilalian News, 1976 (Box-folder 25: 9)
  - Black Dwarf, 1969 (Box-folder 25: 10)
  - Black Express, 1974 (Box-folder 25: 11)
  - Black Fire, 1969 (Box-folder 25: 12)
  - Black Panther, 1967-1991 (Box-folder 25: 13)
  - Black Perspective, 1972 (Box-folder 25: 14)
  - Black Star Liberation Press, 1970 (Box-folder 25: 15)
  - Black Thoughts (Box-folder 25: 16)
  - Black Unity, 1969 (Box-folder 25: 17)
  - Body Politic, 1975 (Box-folder 25: 18)
  - Bolshevik (Box-folder 25: 19)
  - Bond, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 25: 20)
  - Book Review, 1970 (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Bowditch Review, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 26: 2)
  - Breakthrough, 1969 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Bridge, 1975 (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - Broadsheet, 1967 (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - Broadside, 1968 (Box-folder 26: 6)
  - Brother, 1971 (Box-folder 26: 7)
  - Bulletin (Workers League), 1975 (Box-folder 26: 8)
  - Caliche, 1969 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - California Citizen Sun, 1975 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - California Observer, 1965 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - California Voice, 1980 (Box-folder 26: 12)
  - Call Box, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 26: 13)
  - CAMP, 1972 (Box-folder 26: 14)
  - Campus CORE-lator, 1965 (Box-folder 26: 15)
  - Canadian Worker, 1973 (Box-folder 26: 16)
  - Capitalism Stinks, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 26: 17)
  - Catholic Voice, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 26: 18)
  - Catholic Worker, 1968 (Box-folder 26: 19)
  - CAW!, 1968 (Box-folder 26: 20)
  - CDC Bulletin, 1976 (Box-folder 26: 21)
  - Central Valley Voice, 1972 (Box-folder 26: 22)
  - Challenge, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 26: 23)
  - Change, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 26: 24)
  - Changes, 1974 (Box-folder 26: 25)
  - Chicano Student Movement, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Chicago Seed, 1969 (Box-folder 27: 2)
  - Chile Newsletter, 1969 (Box-folder 27: 3)
  - Chingari, 1973 (Box-folder 27: 4)
  - CHISPAS, 1975 (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - Citizen, 1966 (Box-folder 27: 6)
  - Class Struggle (CSL), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Class Struggle (Palo Alto), 1970 (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Coalition News, 1969 (Box-folder 27: 9)
  - Combat Ethnic Weapons, 1971 (Box-folder 27: 10)
  - Combat: Voice of American Conscience, 1966 (Box-folder 27: 11)
  - Come-Unity, 1972 (Box-folder 27: 12)
  - Commemorator, 1991 (Box-folder 27: 13)
  - Commentator, 1975 (Box-folder 27: 14)
  - CNVA-West Bulletin, 1967 (Box-folder 27: 15)
  - Committee to Support Middle East Liberation Newsletter, 1970 (Box-folder 27: 16)
  - Common Sense (People's Bicentennial Commission), 1975 (Box-folder 27: 17)
  - Common Sense (San Francisco), 1974-1977
    - 1974-1975 (Box-folder 27: 18)
    - 1976 (Box-folder 27: 19)
    - 1977-1978 (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Common Woman, 1971 (Box-folder 28: 2)
  - Communiqué for New Politics, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 28: 3)
  - Community Communications Gathering Directory (Box-folder 28: 4)
  - Contempt!, 1970 (Box-folder 28: 5)
  - CORE Southern Newsletter, 1965 (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - CORE-lator, 1965 (Box-folder 28: 7)
  - Counterdraft, 1968 (Box-folder 28: 8)
  - Counterpoint, 1969 (Box-folder 28: 9)
  - Country Press, 1971 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Crisis, 1971 (Box-folder 28: 11)
  - Daily Californian, 1968, 1982 (Box-folder 28: 12)
  - Daily Gater, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 28: 13)
  - Declassified, 1969 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - Despite Everything, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Dimensions, 1968 (Box-folder 28: 16)
  - Dock of the Bay, 1969 (Box-folder 29: 1-4)
  - Drivers Examiner, 1974 (Box-folder 29: 5)
  - East Bay Band Calendar, 1980 (Box-folder 29: 6)
  - East Bay Bridge, 1974 (Box-folder 29: 7)
  - East Bay Labor Journal (Box-folder 29: 8)
  - East Bay Review, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 29: 9)
  - East Bay Voice, 1976-1978
    - 1976 (Box-folder 30: 1)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 30: 2)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 30: 3)
  - East Village Other, 1968-1971
    - 1968-1969 (Box-folder 30: 4)
    - 1969-1971 (Box-folder 30: 5)
  - Ecology, 1970 (Box-folder 30: 6)
  - Ecosphere, 1970 (Box-folder 30: 7)
  - El Gallo, 1969 (Box-folder 30: 8)
  - El Gaucho, 1969 (Box-folder 30: 9)
  - El Grito del Norte, 1969-1973
    - 1969-1971 (Box-folder 30: 10)
    - 1972-1973 (Box-folder 30: 11)
  - El Inmigrante militante, 1974 (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - El Malcriado, 1966-1974
    - 1966-1973 (Box-folder 31: 2)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 31: 3)
  - El Noticiero, 1973 (Box-folder 31: 4)
  - El Pocho Che, 1969 (Box-folder 31: 5)
  - El Tecolote, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 31: 6)
  - El Young Lord, 1971 (Box-folder 31: 7)
  - Electric News, 1969 (Box-folder 31: 8)
  - Emeryville City News, 1980 (Box-folder 31: 9)
  - Employee Press, 1968-1977
    - 1968-1970 (Box-folder 31: 10)
    - 1971-1977 (Box-folder 31: 11)
  - Encore, 1973 (Box-folder 31: 12)
  - Enlisted Times, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 32: 1)
  - Environment (Box-folder 32: 2)
  - Environmental Outcry, 1970 (Box-folder 32: 3)
  - Esalen, 1974 (Box-folder 32: 4)
  - Everywoman, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 32: 5)
  - Exodus, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 6)
  - Express, 1981-1984
    - 1981-1982 (Box-folder 32: 7)
    - 1982 (Box-folder 32: 8-9)
    - 1982-1983 (Box-folder 32: 10)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 33: 1)
    - 1984 (Box-folder 33: 2)
  - Eyewitness, 1971 (Box-folder 33: 3)
  - Fag Rag, 1971 (Box-folder 33: 4)
  - Fateh, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 33: 5)
  - Fatigue Press, 1971 (Box-folder 33: 6)
  - Favorite Sons, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 33: 7)
  - Feminist, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 33: 8)
  - Fifth Estate, 1969 (Box-folder 33: 9)
  - Fifth Wheel, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 33: 10)
  - Fight Back!, 1974 (Box-folder 33: 11)
  - Finally Got the News, 1975 (Box-folder 33: 12)
  - Fire and Police Research Association of Los Angeles Bulletin, 1969 (Box-folder 33: 13)
  - Fire Next Time, 1969 (Box-folder 33: 14)
  - Firing Line, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 33: 15)
  - Flatlands, 1966-1967
    - 1966 (Box-folder 33: 16-17)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 34: 1)
  - Flatlands Democrat, 1968 (Box-folder 34: 2)
  - Folio, 1975 (Box-folder 34: 3)
  - Forward!, 1976 (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - Foundation Bulletin, 1968 (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - Four Lights, 1967 (Box-folder 34: 6)
  - Free Environment, 1975 (Box-folder 34: 7)
  - Free Palestine, 1969 (Box-folder 34: 8)
  - Free Student, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 34: 9)
  - Free Student Union, 1965 (Box-folder 34: 10)
  - Free Water, 1970 (Box-folder 34: 11)
  - Free You, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 34: 12)
  - Freedom (Church of Scientology), 1974-1983 (Box-folder 34: 13)
  - Freedom: Anarchist Weekly, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 34: 14)
  - Friday Ramparts, 1968 (Box-folder 34: 15)
  - Friendship Journal, 1975 (Box-folder 34: 16)
  - Frontline, 1983 (Box-folder 34: 17)
  - F.U.B. (Free University of Berkeley), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 34: 18)
  - Gaceta Sandinista, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - Gadfly, 1971 (Box-folder 35: 2)
  - GASP News, 1976 (Box-folder 35: 3)
  - Gay Sparks, 1975 (Box-folder 35: 4)
  - Gay Sunshine, 1970 (Box-folder 35: 5)
  - Gentle Strength, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 35: 6)
  - GI News, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 35: 7)
  - GI Press Service, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 35: 8-9)
  - Glad Rag, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 35: 10)
  - Glimpse, 1976 (Box-folder 35: 11)
  - Grapevine, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 35: 12)
  - Grass Roots Forum, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 35: 13)
  - Great Speckled Bird, 1969 (Box-folder 35: 14)
  - Grove Street Grapevine, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 35: 15)
  - Guild Notes, 1975 (Box-folder 35: 16)
  - H. du B. Reports, 1967 (Box-folder 35: 17)
  - Ha-Orah-The Light, 1970 (Box-folder 35: 18)
  - Harambee, 1966 (Box-folder 35: 19)
  - Hard Times, 1969 (Box-folder 35: 20)
  - Health Rights News, 1971 (Box-folder 35: 21)
  - High School Student Mobilizer, 1971 (Box-folder 35: 22)
  - Highlander, 1969 (Box-folder 35: 23)
  - Huli, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 35: 24)
  - Humanist, 1973 (Box-folder 35: 25)
  - I. F. Stone's Weekly, 1969 (Box-folder 36: 1)
  - Illustrated Paper, 1966 (Box-folder 36: 2)
  - Independent Labor News, 1977 (Box-folder 36: 3)
  - Independent Socialist, 1967 (Box-folder 36: 4)
  - India Now, 1978 (Box-folder 36: 5)
  - Indians of All Tribes, 1970 (Box-folder 36: 6)
  - Indochina Focal Point, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 36: 7-8)
  - Industrial Worker, 1969-1991 (Box-folder 36: 9)
  - Inside/Outside, 1974 (Box-folder 36: 10)
  - Instant News Service, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 36: 11)
  - Insurgent, 1965 (Box-folder 36: 12)
  - International Bulletin, 1977 (Box-folder 36: 13)
  - International Socialist, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 36: 14-15)
  - Iranian Student Bulletin, 1976 (Box-folder 36: 16)
  - Irish American, 1976 (Box-folder 36: 17)
  - I.S.C. Newsletter (Independent Socialist Club), 1965 (Box-folder 36: 18)
  - It Ain't Me Babe, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 36: 19)
  - Janus, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 37: 1)
  - Jewish Radical, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 37: 2-3)
  - Jihad News, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 4)
  - Journal of Contemporary Revolutions, 1967 (Box-folder 37: 5)
  - Kalayaan International, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 37: 6-7)
  - Keep Left, 1968 (Box-folder 37: 8)
  - LA, 1972 (Box-folder 37: 9)
  - L.A. Student Mobilizer (Box-folder 37: 10)
  - La Causa, 1970 (Box-folder 37: 11)
  - La Chispa, 1971 (Box-folder 37: 12)
  - La Hormiga, 1968 (Box-folder 37: 13)
  - La Raza, 1970 (Box-folder 37: 14)
  - La Voz del Pueblo, 1971 (Box-folder 37: 15)
  - Labor News, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 38: 1)
  - Labor Pulse, 1976 (Box-folder 38: 2)
  - Labyrinth, 1977 (Box-folder 38: 3)